-커부-D.C 기미갤
베포자유 수정금지 피드백환영
너희 5명 체포됬다!
손 등뒤로해!
You five are under arrest!
Hands behind your back!
수갑채워! 아프게해!(?)
Cuff 'em, boys! Make it hurt!
뭐해! 그대로 있어!
Come on! Keep them like that!
크리스 디아즈!
Chris Diaz!
트레이시 내쉬
Traci Nash.
게일 팩
Gail Peck.
- 도브 엡스틴
- 뭐하는거에요?
- Dov Epstein.
- What the hell?
그리고 앤디 맥넬리
And Andy McNally.
너희들은 닥치고있을 권리가있고
You have the right to shut up.
너희들은 조용히 있을 권리가있고
You have the right to remain calm,
그리고 수갑을 벗을
권리가 있다
and you have the right to
get out of these handcuffs
어떻게 해서든 니들이 아는데로
any way you know how!
후!
Whoo!
니들중 제일먼저 수갑을
빠져나오는 신입은 맥주 무료
First rookie out of their
cuffs drinks for free.
예에!
Yeah!
나머지는 돈내는 거다!
Everyone else pays!
- 준비됬나?
- 네!
- Are you ready?
- Yeah!
On your mark, get set, go to town!
신호맞춰서, 준비, 시작!
Steve, Steve! I happen to know that
스티브x2 나 우연히 내 오빠가
여벌의 키를
가지고있는거 알아 나한테줘
my brother has an extra
key. Give me they key.
너희들이 수갑채울꺼면
너희들이 수갑 벗어나올줄도 알아야지
You can put 'em on, you
gotta be able to get 'em off.
You have to... come on.
Partner it up, partner it up!
여기서 뭐하는거야 팩?
What is going on here, Peck?
나 아무것도 안했어
I'm not doing anything.
Ohh!
Yeah!
믿기지가않는군
Unbelievable!
신사 숙녀 여러분
Ladies and gentlemen,
15사단의 신입들 입니다!
meet the rookies of 15 division!
바에서 거금을
지불하라고 할꺼야
Oh, this bar bill's
gonna cost me a fortune.
네 수당 나도 알지
I know. Your entire allowance.
앤디, 너 털렸어
Andy, you were robbed.
알아,사기꾼한테 Robo-cheater 한테
Mm, yeah, by the cheater. Robo-cheater.
있지?
You know what?
할수있는대로
어떻게든 빠져나가랬잖아 그러니 뭐
He said any way you know
how anyway, so whatever.
이 직업 진짜 좋다 알지?
I love this job so much, you know?
좀웃기지만 여기있는
사람들 다 정말 좋다
It's funny, but I love
all these guys so much.
- 너 알지도 못하잖아
- 상관없어 우린 벌써 형제들이야
- You don't even know them.
- It doesn't matter we're already brothers.
- 나도 그래. 형제
- 숙녀분들도..
- I feel that, brotha.
- And... and sisters.
- 숙녀분들도. 그래
- 순경은 어떻고?
- And sisters. Right there.
- How about officers?
- 순경들
- 예
- Officers.
- Yeah.
- 순경들, yeah!
- 순경들x2
- Officers, yeah!
- Officers. Officers.
여기 우리가 왔다
So here we are.
몇달전동안 우리는 같이 지냈다
We've spent the last few months together
이 직업을 위해 훈련하느라
training to do this job.
어떻게 쏘는지 싸우는지 배웠고
We've learned how to shoot and fight
그리고 경찰차를 빨리 운전하는법도
and drive a police car really fast.
내말은, 우리는 준비됬다
I mean, we're ready.
그들은 계속 우리는
아무것도 모른다고 하지만
I mean, they keep telling
us we don't know anything.
- 상관없어...
- 아카데미에서 얼마나
잘했나는 상관없다
- It doesn't matter...
- That it doesn't matter how
well we did at the academy.
너가 legacy고
안이나 밖에서 너가 이 직업을 안다고
That you might be a legacy
and think you know the job
생각하고
길거리를 잘알고 있고
inside and out. Maybe
you're hip to the street.
너가 마일밖의 종이타겟을
쏠 수 있겠지
Maybe you can shoot a paper
target from a mile away.
사실 상관없다
It actually doesn't matter.
길거리의 생활에 대한 삶을
There is absolutely no training
준비해주는 연습은 없다
that prepares you for life on the street.
그리고 그게 주의사항이다
환영한다 15사단
And on that cautionary
note, welcome to 15.
봉사하고, 보호하고...
Serve, protect...
그리고 망치지 마라
And don't screw up.
- 긴장했어? -아니
-당연히 아니지 ,넌 빌어먹을 기계니깐
- Nope.
- Of course not. You're a frickin' machine.
트레이스 우리 차에타서
그들이 운전해줄꺼야
무슨일이라도 일어나면
Traci, we get in the
car. They drive us around.
그들이 어떻게할지 알려줄꺼야
-난 뭐해야할지 알아
- I mean, anything happens,
they tell us what to do.
- I know what to do.
아카데미에서 3달동안
I spent three months at the academy
정확이 뭘해야되는지 준비해왔어
preparing myself for exactly what to do.
- 모든것을 위해 준비
- Ready for anything.
크리스 디아즈
Chris Diaz.
맥주6병,위스트 2명에
다량의 이혼 서류
Six beers, two whiskeys and a
stack of brand-new divorce papers.
어..Sir?
Uh... sir?
어제밤 득점표지
Last night's scorecard.
내가 인내심이 그렇게
넘치지 않다는거지
Means I'm not exactly
overflowing with patience,
공동체정신,일의 스릴이지
team spirit, thrill of the job.
갈까?
Shall we?
어,어,네 가야겠죠
Uh, uh, yeah, guess I'm going.
- 그럼 나중에 보자고 알겠지?
- 안녕하세요
- Okay, so I'll see you later, all right?
- Hi.
멋지네 내가 거리의 제니퍼(노래)를 가졌네
Great. I get Jenny from the block.
그 가방은 내 차에 못타
That is not coming in my car.
- 이름이 뭐라고 했지?
- 맥넬리입니다,sir
- What was your name again?
- McNally, sir.
- 맥넬리 그리고 같이..
- 앤디 맥넬리입니다 둘다 상관없습니다
- McNally, and as in...
- Andy McNally. Either one's fine.
그럼 알려줘서 고맙군
앤디 맥넬리
Okay, well, thanks for
the update, Andy McNally.
- 가지
- 네
- Let's go.
- Okay.
가방은..?
Oh. The bag?
뒤로
In the back.
있지,사람들은 새로운
경찰 냄새를 맡을수있어
You know, people can smell new cops
그들이 새로운 페인트 냄새를 맡는것처럼
like they can smell fresh paint.
보기에도 새로워 보이고
듣기에도 새로워 보이지
You look new. You sound new.
우리가 새거죠
We are new.
알아 알지 내말이 그거야
I know. I know. That's my point.
- 그래서 우리가 이야기를 나눠야 되는거야
- 무슨 이야기요?
- That's why we have to have the talk.
- What talk?
"날 당황하게 하지마
너 라디오가 벨트의 잘못된 방향에
The "don't embarrass me, your
radio is on the wrong side
있고, 내가 말한데로하되
내가 하는데로 하지말아" 이야기
of your belt, uh, do as
I say, not as I do" talk.
미확인 문제가 있다
We have a trouble unknown
제임슨과 킹 근처 306 Dunn Avenue
306 Dunn Avenue near Jameson and King.
- 가능한 유닛 있나?
- 저기요, 바로 저기에요
- Is there a unit available to attend?
- Hey, that's right over there.
306은 구멍이야
Yeah, 306 is a hole.
I was there twice last week
for drunk and disorderly.
지난주에 2번이나 음주랑
난동피우는것 때문에 갔었어
We're gonna let Noelle take that one,
노엘이 처리하게 놔둘꺼야
너랑 나랑은 커피나 마시러 갈꺼고
and you and I are gonna go have a coffee.
- 이야기를 계속 나눌꺼야
- 네
- We're gonna continue to have the talk.
- Okay.
1519, 10-8에 아직인가?
응답할수있나?
1519. Are you 10-8 yet?
Can you take the call?
멋지군,해봐 검은 버튼이야
Terrific. Go ahead. It's the black button.
1519...
- 다른 검은 버튼
- 1519 10-4
- The other black button.
- Oh. 1519, 10-4.
좋나?
Are you happy?
그럼 가볼까
Okay, let's hit it.
내가 한 15분전쯤에 전화했는데
I called you all about 15 minutes ago.
- 네, 안녕
- 안녕
- Okay. Hi.
- Hi.
네, 그럼 무슨일인지 말해보세요
Okay, uh, tell me what's happening.
- 202호말이에요
- 네
- It's apartment 202.
- Uh-huh.
사람들 소리지르는것 없이도
안좋을만큼 안좋아요
It's bad enough in there without
people yelling and screaming.
네,맥넬리 차에서 내려봐
Okay. Um, McNally, get out of the car.
그럼, 사람들이 소리지른다고요
Okay. So people are yelling.
몇몇 남자들이 있는데
서로 노는데
A couple of guys in there.
They're going at each other.
- 네
- 마치 투견같다니깐
- Uh-huh.
- It's like freakin' pit bulls, man.
네 잠깐만,그들이 투견같은건가요
Ok, wait a second, they are like pit bulls
- 아니면 투견을 가지고있나요
- 나도 잘모르겠어요....
- or they have pit bulls?
- Man, I don't know...
누나 경찰이에요?
Are you a policeman?
음..여자란다
officer 경찰우먼
Uh, you know, woman.
Officer. Policewoman/officer.
- 음,내말은,그렇단다
- 총좀 봐도 되요?
- Yeah, I mean, well, yes.
- Can I see your gun?
미안해 이게
진짜 위험한거라 알겠지?
Oh, I'm sorry. It's
really dangerous, okay?
꼭 조심해야
You have to be...
1519 306 Dunn에
총격이 있었다
Ma'am. 1519. We have
shots fired at 306 Dunn.
지원부탁한다
가자, 가자고!
Calling for backup. Come
on. Let's go. Let's go!
빨리!
Now!
내 바로 뒤에 있어
Stay right behind me.
날 보호하는거야 뒤에서 쏘지말고
You cover me. Don't shoot me in the back.
워우!
Whoa!
안으로 들어가서 문닫으세요
Sir, get back inside. Close your door.
1519. 우린 1층에 계단에있다
1519. We're on the first floor,
1층계단을 오르는중이다
about to head up the front stairs,
1505.거의다 왔다
1505. We're almost there.
Sir? sir 총격이 있었는데
지원을 기다려야되지 않나요?
Sir? Sir, gunshots fired.
Shouldn't we wait for backup?
여기에 작은 애들이 있어
We got little kids in this building.
지원기다리고싶으면 가서 기달려
You want to wait for backup, you go ahead.
알아서해
You knock yourself out.
- 그럼 그냥 따라가면 되는거죠
총을 뽑을까요 말까요 ?
- 정말로 ?
- So I just follow you in,
right? Gun in, gun out?
- Really?
죄송해요
Sorry.
1519. 202호에 있다
들어가겠다
1519. We're at apartment
202. We're going in.
- 붙어 붙어 준비됬지?
- 네
- Tug up, tug up. Okay? Ready to go?
- Yeah.
경찰이다 움직이지마!
손 위로 지금당장!
Police. Don't move! Hands
in the air! Do it now!
- 그들은 갔어요 갔다구요!
- 보호해
- Okay, they're gone. They're gone!
- Cover them.
- 그..민크는 저기있어요 그는..
- 새디,새디 진정해요
- Okay. He... Mink's over there. He's... he's...
- All right, Sadie. Sadie, relax. Relax.
손위로해
Okay. Keep your hands up.
움직이지마
Don't move.
그래, oh God
Okay. Oh, God. Uh...
Okay, okay. Sir? Um...
- 들어라,피해자 한명
가슴에 총상
- 거기 있어
- Dispatch, I have one victim,
V.S.A. , shot in the chest.
- Just stay there.
이 빌딩을 봉쇄하고있다
Have responding units seal the building.
살인으로 확인되고 응답하라
Notify homicide and ident.
알겠다
Copy.
Sir?
Sir!
- 뭐?
- 마약 과복용자가 있는것같아요,숨을 겨우쉬어요
- What?
- I think we got an O.D. She's barely breathing.
3미터짜리 막대로도 안건드리겠다
I wouldn't touch her with a 10-foot pole.
- 의료원 올때까지 기달려
- 그냥 어린애에요
- You... you wait for the medics.
- She's just a kid.
일어나, 전 요원 202호는 안전하다
Get up. All units, apartment 202 is clear.
-새디 수갑채울께 알겠지
그럼 채우자고 알겠지?
-Sadie, I gotta cuff you. Okay.
Now let's plug it in, okay?
- 나한테 정확이 무슨일이있었는지 말해줘야되
- 난 몰라요, 여기 없었어요
- You gotta tell me exactly... exactly what happened.
- I don't know, 'cause I wasn't in here.
그래? 그거 웃긴데
왜인줄 알아?
Oh, yeah? Well, that's
funny, because you know what?
- 넌 감옥에 있었어야되니깐
- 지금 집행 유예기간이에요
- You're supposed to be in jail.
- I'm on probation.
One, two, three, four, five...
Six, seven, eight, nine, ten. Come on.
- 우리 진짜 여기 앉아있는거야?
- 나 전화하고있잖아
- We're really just supposed to sit here?
- I'm on the phone.
활동은 전부 놓쳣잖아
We're missing all the action.
저기요,sir
Uh, excuse me. Sir? Hi.
질문이요
제가 궁금한데...
Uh, quick question.
Uh, I was wondering, uh,
- 어떻하면, 제가 괜찮을까요..
- 말해봐
- how would I, and would I be allowed to...
- Spit it out.
오늘밤 제 총을 집에
가져가도 될까요?
Oh. Uh, can I take my
gun home with me at night?
왜지?
Why?
그냥..가지고 있고
익숙해질려고
You know, just to, uh, to
have it, to get used to it,
- 깨끗이 할려고요
- 집으로 가져가기 용지는 2번째 서랍에있다
- to clean it.
- Take-home forms are in the second drawer.
- 다 쓰고나면 내가 결정하지
- 감사합니다
- You fill one out, then I decide.
- Thank you, sir.
대단한데
Big man.
그렇지
Yes, I am.
기록을 위해 순경팩한테
수색을 위해 여자경찰이 필요합니다
Officer Peck to booking. I
need a P.W. to do a search.
P.W....좋네 여자경찰..
P.W.... Great. Policewoman.
축하한다
Congratulations.
어,정말 고마워
Ahh. Thank you very much.
Sir.
조가 잡았어
Picked her up at St. Joe's,
간호사 구역에서 약을 훔치고있었지
stealing drugs from the nurse's station.
신원체크하고 ,
수색한다음 감방에 넣어
Get her tombstone I.D. ,
search her, put her in a cell.
경사는 가는중입니다
Sarge is on his way.
뭐? 여자를 수색할순없잖아
What? I can't search a lady.
그럼..어..이름요
Okay, uh...?
테비 번즈 34살
Tabby Barnes. I'm 34.
930 Church 거리
아파트 1-D에 살고
I live at 930 Church
Street, apartment 1-D,
난 무죄에요 어쨋든
and I'm innocent, by the way.
아니,..물론 그럴거에요
No, I... yeah, I'm sure you are.
어디 다친데는 있나요 테비씨?
Uh, do you have any injuries, Tabby?
약먹는거 있나요?
Are you on any medication?
Finasteride, spironolactone,
premarin, estroegene, estradiol(약이름;)
premarin, estroegene, estradiol.
호르몬
Hormones.
트렌스젠더에요 나
I'm transgendered.
나쁘진 않죠 ?
Not bad, huh?
네...네
No, it's... it's not...
괜찮아요
no, not bad at all.
바로 올께요
I'm gonna be right back.
- 여자 잖아
- 아냐
- She's a chick.
- No.
- 그럼 너가 말하는게..
- 도브 여자아니야, 남자야
- You're saying that...
- Dov, she's not a chick. She's a man.
저 남자아니에요 트렌스젠더에요
I'm not a man. I'm transgendered.
저희한테 그게 정확히
무슨뜻인지 설명해줄래요?
Can you please explain to
us exactly what that means?
제말은,만약..당신이
남자라면 제가 수색할수있죠
I mean, if... if you're
a dude, I could search you.
그리고 아니라면 게일이 하겠죠
And if not, Gail would be delighted.
너가 수색하고,기록해
이건 로켓과학이 아니야
You search her. You book
her. It's not rocket science.
약간 과학이죠..죄송해요
It's some kind of science. Sorry.
지갑있나요?
Got a wallet?
음
Ah.
Tabor Barnes 남자의 남
Tabor Barnes. "M" for male.
죄송해요 제가 아직 갱신을 못해서
I'm sorry, sir. I just haven't updated it.
엡스타인, 니 차례다
Epstein, you're up.
알았어요
Okay.
주변 막아봐
Go ahead. Contain the perimeter.
안에 있는 사람들은요?
그들모두 잠재적인 증인들이잖아요
What about the people inside?
They're all possible witnesses.
- 그럼 그들도 억류해
- 제가 진술서도 받아야될까요?
- So contain 'em. Don't let 'em out.
- Should I start taking statements?
물론,내 일까지 뺏어갈수 있지
Yeah, sure. You can start by taking mine.
준비됬나,테이프 두르고
You read here it is. Put up the tape.
- 라디오앞에 앉아있어
- 1509.여기 뒤 덤블속에
움직임이 있다
- Sit on your radio.
- 1509. We got some movement
in the bushes back here.
오, 와줘서 고맙군
Oh, hey. Thanks for joining.
- 사수를 찾고있었는데 하지만..
- 조용히 해
- We were looking for the shooter, but we...
- Shut it.
- 사수를 찾고 있었어
- 숨 안쉬고 있는줄알았는데
- We were looking for the shooter.
- Thought she wasn't breathing.
- 안쉬고있었어요
제가 인공호흡을 해줬죠 - EW
- She wasn't, but I gave
her mouth-to-mouth. - Ew.
코트니 러브는 여기서 나가게 해주자고
Let's get Courtney love out of here,
- 안에 있는 남자는 아무대도 안가니깐
- 정말? 나 힐링파워있는데
- 'cause the guy in there is not going anywhere.
- You sure? I got healing powers.
내가 그렇게 들은거지
키스해서 고쳐줘x2
That's what I hear. Kiss
it better. Kiss it better.
여기있는 우리친구 새디말로는
According to our friend Sadie here,
피해자 이름은 민크 버커고...
잘알려진 마약딜러에
Victim's name is Mink Barker...
well-known drug dealer.
친구랑 같이 들어왔다고해
지금은 그게 의심하고있는거지
Came in with a friend.
Right now that's our suspect.
백인에,기름끼 머리
He's a white male, greasy black hair,
검은 머리에 그리고
벌써 멀리갔을거야
black t-shirt, and he
is probably long gone.
맥넬리랑 네쉬, 너희 둘은
McNally, Nash, we need you guys to clear
여기 정리좀해
아무도 못나가.전부 억류해
the rest of the house. No one
leaves. Contain the premises.
그럼 조심하고 길잃어버리지마
Okay. Yeah, be careful. Don't get lost.
가,가
Go. Go.
그럼..우리 그냥 둘러보면되는거야?
So what, we just... we start lookin'?
그래 위에서부터 밑으로 가자
Yeah, start at the top, work our way dow
그리고,사수가 아직 빌딩에
있을지도 모르니 총은 들고
And, uh, shooter could still be
in the building, so guns drawn.
확인하기까지 가장해야지
Fake it till you make it.
어...
Uh...
무서워?
You scared?
아니, 너는?
No. Are you?
- 아니
- 웃기네
- No.
- Yeah, right.
그럼 준비됬지?
All right. Ready?
응
Okay.
- 넌 끝에있는거 맡아 난 이거 맡을께
- 알았어
- You take the door on the other end of this.
- Okay.
- 경찰이다! 문열어!
- Police! Open up!
실례합니다 그냥 주변을
둘러봐야합니다
Excuse me, ma'am. I just need
to take a look at the premises.
Uh...
경찰이다! 문열어!
Police! Open up!
노크완전 구리내
That is a crappy lock.
움직이지말고 손올려
Don't move. Put your hands up.
움직이지 말라고했잖아! 거기있어!
I said don't move! Stay where you are!
-나중에봐 -안돼 멈춰!
See ya. No, I... stop!
가자
Here we go.
너...
You...
- 움직이지마!
- 움직이면 어쩔건데
- I said don't move!
- Or what?
트레이시!
Traci!
앤디 맥넬리, 3층에있다
Uh, Andy McNally. I'm on the third floor.
소방계단으로 도망가는
두명 남자가 있다
I've got two guys running
down the fire escape.
그중한명은
인상착의가 동일하다
Uh, one of them matches
the subject's description.
땅에 누구없나? 트레이시!
Anybody on the ground? Traci!
오
Oh!
지금 계단을 내려가고있다
Guys, I'm running down the fire escape.
용의자를 추격하고있다
검은 셔츠에 기름기진 머리
I'm in pursuit of a suspect...
black t-shirt, greasy hair.
여기는 사건현장입니다
Oh! Oh! Sir, this is a crime scene.
여기서 나가라고
말해야겠네요
I'm gonna have to ask you
to turn this thing around.
- 형사님?
- 살인담당
- Detective?
- Homicide.
알아서 가세요
Help yourself.
앤디?
Andy?
야?
Dude?
어디야?
Where are you?
앤디?
Andy?
내가 지금 어리둥절해하고 있으면...
Okay, if I am being hazed right now...
경찰이다! 움직이지마!
Police! Don't move!
알았어 미안해
나도..난 생각이 짧았어
Okay, look, I'm sorry.
I... I wasn't thinking.
352 Dunn 지원부탁한다
Backup. 352 Dunn.
내가 대체 어떻게 해야됬어?
What was I supposed to do?
알았어 알았어 진정해
Okay, okay, calm down.
경찰이다 움직이지마!
손위로 올려 당장!
Police! Don't move! Put
your hands up right now!
지금 빨리!
둘다 철장에 마주보고서!
Hurry up! Now! Put 'em
against the fence, both of you.
아 뭐야...
이러면 안되지...
Aw, come on. I don't...
I don't believe this.
조용히하세요
Sir, be quiet.
Oh! Aah!
움직이지마!
철조망으로 돌아가 빨리!
Don't move! Get back
to the fence right now!
- 이러고 싶지 않을거야
- 시끄러 뒤돌아
- You don't want to do this.
- Shut up. Turn over.
진짜로 날 믿어줘야된다니깐
I'm serious. You gotta trust me, okay?
난 진지해 그러니깐 닥쳐
No, I'm serious. You shut up.
체포됬다
Resisting arrest.
현장을 도망쳤어
Fleeing the scene. Ohh.
Oh.
가지고있네
Possession.
Ow, ow, ow!
총은 어딨어 응?
Where's the gun, huh?
총 없어. 나 지금 일하고있다니깐
I don't have a gun. I'm on the job.
더이상은 아니지 일어나
Not anymore. Get up.
- 빨리 일어나
- 그거 아프잖아
- Come on, get up.
- Aah. That hurts.
가
Go.
가자고
Let's go.
그래 그래 고맙네
Okay, okay. Thank you.
Sir.
무전하려고 했었어요
I've been trying to radio you.
그래 여기 돌아봐
보이지? 이거 켜봐
Yeah? Here, turn around.
Ah, see? Try turning it on.
제가 몇명 체포했어요
Listen, I've made a couple of arrests.
- 차뒤에있어요
- 체포?
- They're in the back of the car.
- Arrests?
- 네
- 뭐에대해서?
- Yeah.
- For what?
현장에서 도망
마약, 범인이랑 딱맞아요
Fleeing the scene.
Possession. One guy matches
- 증인이 말했던거요
- 그래?
- the subject description.
- Really?
네
Okay.
그럼 걔들 넣어두자고
Yeah, let's get 'em
back to the barn, yeah.
- 배고파 죽겠어
- 저기..
- I'm starving.
- Uh, you know,
현장을 아무도
못나가게 하라고하셔서
because you said don't let
anybody leave the scene...
나도 내가뭐라고했는지 알고싶어
쿠키 먹을래?
I know what I said. What
do you want, a cookie?
1503, 확인했나?
1503, do you copy?
놀랍네
Amazing.
뭐?
What?
아냐...아냐
좋은일이야..
Nothing. No, that's...
that's... that's good work.
- 감사해요
- 그래
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
이나쁜놈들 기록하자고
Let's book these bad boys.
나 방금 여자
감옥에서 나온거 알죠
You know, I just got
out of ladies' prison.
- 당신이 3달동안
처음으로 만지는 남자에요
- 디아즈,새디 만나봐
- You're the first man that
I've touched in three months.
- Diaz, meet Sadie Falls.
증인이야
방금 감옥나왔어
She's a witness. She
just got out of prison.
진술서 받고 수색해
Take her statement and search her.
네 알겠습니다
저랑 가시죠
Yes, sir. Will do. Okay,
ma'am. Come with me.
Okay.
이아이 여기 안살아요
안그럴꺼에요
Well, he doesn't live
here... not a chance.
저 운동화보세요
150불은 그냥 넘어가죠
Look at his running shoes...
top of the line. 150 bucks easy.
아동복지국에 전화해
Calling children's aid.
말하는게 좋을꺼야 꼬마야
You better start talking, young man.
그럼 조 누나한테
얘기해보렴
Okay, Joe, you gotta
start talking to me, okay?
안돼요
I can't.
어째서?
How come?
약속했어요
I promised.
누구랑 말이니?
You promised who?
누나한테 말해도 된단다
You can tell me.
놀이중이었어요
I was playing a game.
으음
Mm-hmm.
이 놀이에서는..
And in the game, you're s...
옷장에 있어야 해요
you're supposed to stay in the closet
그가 저를 찾기 전까지요
until he comes and finds you.
누가 너를 찾기 전까지?
Until who comes and finds you?
이 아파트로 다른남자가
들어오는걸 봤다는건가요?
Are you saying you saw a different
guy come into the apartment?
아뇨 아무것도
말하지 않을거에요
No, I'm saying that I'm not
gonna tell you anything else
당신이 나를 도와준다고
약속하지 않는이상
until you promise to help me out of here.
형사법에 의하면,
Ma'am, according to the criminal code,
법적으로
보고할 의무가 있습니다
you are under legal
obligations to report everything
- 건물안에서 본것 전부를요
- 당신 귀엽군요, 프랭크
- you saw in there.
- You are adorable. Hey, Frank.
프랭크?
Frank?
뭔데?
What's the problem?
아니 그냥 신입이랑
거래가 안되서
No, it's just I can't, like,
make a deal with a rookie.
- 나랑 거래하면 되지말해봐
뭘봤는데 잘못한거 없어
- 나 기록하지 않을거지?
- So make a deal with me. Tell me
what you saw. No harm, no foul.
- You're not gonna write me up?
알았어
Okay.
꼬맹이가 와선 민크를 찾았어
엄청 화나있었지
Kid came in. He was looking for
Mink. He was real pissed off.
인상착이는 말랐고
He was a, uh, uh, a skinny guy,
갈색머리에 주황색 셔츠
um, brown hair, orange t-shirt.
한 5분뒤에
총이 발사됬지
About five minutes
later, the gun went off.
다른방에 있었어
자기 나 맹세해
I was in the other room.
Sweetie, I swear to God,
무슨일이 있었는지 못봤어
I didn't see what happened.
- 정말 못봤어 맹세해
- 알았어 x3
- I didn't see what happened, I swear.
- Okay. Okay, okay.
하지만
안내서가 우린 꼭..
But, sir, the manual
says that you have to...
- "하지만 안내서가 우린... "
- 보세요 그녀가 증거를 감추고있었어요
- "But, sir, the manual says... "
- Listen, she was withholding evidence.
알어 너한테서 부터
말단, 어쩔 때는
Yeah, from you. Look,
rook, sometimes you gotta
약간 주고 조금 받는거야
알겠지? 좋아
give a little to get a
little, all right? All right.
- 쟤한테 진술서써줘
- 내가 그 남자 신분확인할수있어요
- Give him the statement.
- I can I.D. the guy.
빨리 이놈들 철차 밟자고
Let's get these guys processed.
맥넬리,넌 저놈을 맡아
Now, McNally, you got that guy.
가자 빨리 움직여
Come on. Let's go. Move it.
Good stuff. Good stuff.
- 그럼 내가 이놈부터 구류실에 넣을게
- 기록부터 해야되지 않나요?
- Okay. I am gonna get this guy into a holding cell.
- Don't we have to book him first?
- 보통은 그렇지
- 좋아요 이제 제가 데려갈께요,잘했어
- Yeah, usually.
- That's cool, officers. I'll take it from here. Nice work.
- 뭐가 안좋은줄알아? 내가 맡는다고 했잖아
- 아뇨 저는...
- You know what's not cool? I said that I got him.
- No, I...
제프는 어딨어
넌 누구야, 헤이 샘
Uh, where's Jeff? Who the
hell are you? Hey, Sam. Buddy.
마약 수사반이 널 다시 준다니
믿기지 않는데, 집에 잘왔어
I can't believe the drug squad's
giving you back. Welcome home.
내말은,난 ...
I mean, 'cause I haven't...
내가 멀리 보낸논
이후론 못봤거든
I haven't seen you here
since I put you away.
경찰이야?
You're a cop?
경찰?
A cop?
- 아냐 닥치고있어
- Are you serious?
- No. Shut up.
- 젠장 여기서 쟤가 뭐하고있는거야?
- 난 구류실로 데려갈려고 했어
- What the hell is he doing here?
- I was trying to get him into a holding cell.
약간 경고라도 주지
그랬어 어?
Maybe a little heads-up
would be in order.
어떻게 그럴수 있어
How could you?
- 조용히해 전부 닥쳐
- 미안하다 미안해
- Shut up! Everybody, shut up.
- Sorry, buddy. Sorry.
- 샘 내가 정말 미안해...
- 어떻게 생각했어 ?
- Sam, I'm so sorry. I...
- What do you think?
펑크처럼 입고 거기서있는데
I'm standing there dressed like a punk.
수갑도 채워있고 내가 아직
잠복중이라는 증거가 많았는데
I'm in cuffs. Many would
assume I'm still undercover.
제 잘못입니다
Sir, it was my fault.
쟤는 말단이라고 혼자
그렇게 돌아다니면 안돼잖아
She's a rook. She's not supposed
to be running around on her own.
샘,나도알아 약간 느슨했어
Sam, I know. It got kinda stretched out.
- 내가 집을 수색하라고했어
- 그리고 그가 인상착이랑 동일했어요
- I asked her to clear the house.
- And he matched the description.
- 제가 잡았죠, 하지만 전 몰랐어요
- 내가 말했잖아
"지금 실수하는거야" 라고
- I arrested him, but I didn't know.
- I... I told you, "don't do this.
You're makin' a mistake."
- 범죄자들이 다 그렇게 말하죠 그렇지않나요?
- 그게 걔들이 말하던거였나?
- Okay, well, everybody says that, don't they?
- Is that what they say?
왜 그냥 잠복중이라고
말하지 그랬어요?
Why didn't you just tell me
you were working undercover?
내가 지금 일하고있다고 말햇잖아
I told you I was on the job.
내가 정확이 말해줄순없잖아
I couldn't exactly break it down for you.
내 동료가 바로 저기있는데
거리에서 제일 말많은애
My guy was right there...
biggest mouth on the street,
그래서 내 동료인, 8개월동안
which is why he's my guy. Eight months.
8개월동안 잠복근무,
Eight months undercover,
- 쓰레기에서 살고, 정보모으려고 노력하고
- 죄송해요
- living in a hole, cultivating informants...
- Okay, well, I'm sorry.
마침내 사람들이..마침내 사람들이
나한테 말하기 시작하는데
Finally getting people... finally
getting people to talk to me,
그런데 왠 사슴이 첫날에 혼자와서
and some Bambi comes along first day,
자기 생각으로만 경찰을
체포했지, 영웅이 되고싶어서
arrests a cop from her own
division, trying to be a hero.
고맙네, 영원히 친구하자고
Thanks, pal. Friends forever.
자 여기 25센트보이지?
All right, little man.
You see this quarter?
어느손에 있는지 알면
너가 가질수 있단다
If you can guess what hand
it's in, you can keep it.
- 하지만 잘봐 난 마술사니깐
- 아뇨 내가 말했잖아요 키를 가지고있다니까요
- But be careful. I'm a magician.
- No, I'm telling you, I've got a key.
꽤 화려한 키에요
60불짜리
It's one of the fancy
keys at 60 bucks a pop.
코드없이는 복사본도 못만들죠
Can't get 'em duplicated without a code.
In... my... sleeve.
내 소매에 있지
아뇨 코드는 없어요
No, I don't have the code,
하지만 키에 무슨 숫자가있는데
but there's a number on the key. It...
Okay, buddy, look at your caller I.D.
있지 저기 전화온 아이디를 봐봐
Yeah, it says "police.
" Do you want know why?
그래 경찰이라고 하지
왜그런지 알아?
'Cause I'm the frickin' police,
내가 빌어먹을 경찰이니깐
그리고 내가 말하잖아
주소가 필요하다고
and I'm telling you
that I need an address.
기록하는덴 저기야
Booking's that way.
살인현장 증인이야
Uh, she's a witness to a homicide
집행유예는 어긴적이 없는...
who has definitely not breached probation.
아직..아직 그녀를 수색하야되
We, uh, you still need to search her...
조심해
Carefully.
- 당신이 해도되
- 어 그리고 프랭크가 수갑채우은 채우래
- You can search me.
- Oh, and, uh, Frank says to make her cough.
알잖아 그냥 대비해서...
You know, just in case she's got, um,
drugs up the... the ying-yang.
내가 빌어먹을 경찰이고
I am the frickin' police,
조한테줄 주소를 얻었어
and I have an address for Joe!
Yay
Yay.
Yes!
그게 나아지게 하나요 네?
Is that working for you, huh?
때리거나 두드리는게 ?
당신 뜻은 알겠어요
All the slamming and banging?
I mean, I get your point.
- 여기서 뭐하는거야?
- 끊질기게 굴고있죠
- What are you doing in here?
- I'm being persistent.
있죠 난 오늘
잘될거 하나도 없어요
You know, I have nothing
else going for me today,
- 그래서 의심간다면..
- 여자 가이드 안좋아해
- so, you know, when in doubt...
- I don't like girl guides.
I don't like being raked over coals
for not knowing the secret handshake.
혼자 위로하세요
난 아마도 짤릴테니깐
You know, console yourself.
I'll probably be fired.
있죠 그 집엔 아직
죽은 남자가 누워있고
You know what? There's still
a dead guy lying in that house.
오 그리고 자유게
도망치는 남자도 있네요 총이랑같이
Oh, and there's another guy
running free and clear with a gun.
그래서 이게 당신
이랑 맞지않는다면
So whenever you feel like
this is out of your system,
아마도 5분만이라도
경찰처럼 행동해야죠
maybe you'd care to act
like a cop for five minutes.
넌 5분밖에 경찰된지 안됬잖아
I've only been a cop for five minutes.
뭘 알고있죠?
What do you know?
넌 뭐알고있는데
What do you got?
- 피해자이름은 민크 바커에요
- 와우 민크 바커
- Victim's name is Mink Barker.
- Whoo! Mink Barker.
그게 민크바커면 생일축하해
If it's Mink Barker, happy birthday.
놀라운걸 나쁜 헤로인에 왕이고
고통주는데도 왕이지
It was a big surprise. King
of bad dope. King of pain.
넌 더러운 죽음을 좋아할
이웃들을 다 가졌네
You got half a neighborhood
who'd love to see the creep dead.
그놈 형편없지 길거리레벨의
Guy's a sleazebag. Deals... deals a ton
- 마약을 다루지, 좋은건 없어
- 잠깐만요,그럼 좋은 마약도 있나요?
- of junk at street level, none of it's good.
- Hold on a sec. There's good junk?
물론
쥐약도 안들어있고
Yeah, there's heroin that
hasn't been cut with rat poison,
유리가루나 다른약도 안들은것들 어쨋든
cut glass, other drugs, you name it.
3주전에 seven O.DS 가 있었는데
We've had seven O. Ds in three weeks...
전부 바커물건이었지만
이제 걔는 죽었으니 카르마가 나쁜놈이지
it's all Barker's stuff. Now
he's dead. Karma's a bitch.
그럼 총쏜사람은요
Okay. So then what about the gunman?
분명히 다른
남자랑 왔을텐데
I mean, apparently he came
in with some other guy...
기름진 머리 있잖아요
그게 제가 당신이라고 생각한 이유에요
you know, greasy black hair.
That's why I thought it was you.
그건 마이크 월척이야, 족제비야
That's Mike Kowalchuk. He's a weasel,
하지만 걘 총도 없고
남자도 아니지
but he doesn't have a gun
and he doesn't have the balls,
그리고 이건 젤이거든
and this is gel, by the way.
어 그럼 오렌지 셔츠
입은 아이는?
So, uh, what about the
kid in the orange t-shirt?
누굴 얘기하는지 모르겠는데요
I don't know who you're talking about.
총소리 듣고 창문봤더니
Heard the shots, looked out the window,
몇몇애들이 소방계단으로
내려가는거 봤는데
saw a couple of kids taking
off down the fire escape.
걔중 한명은 빈 빌딩으로 들어가던데
One of 'em ran into an empty building.
- 총숨기기에 좋은 장소지
- 좋아요, 어느 빈빌딩이요?
- It's a good place to hide a gun.
- Okay, which empty building?
오른쪽 근처 빌딩말야
나한테 태클걸어서
You know, the one right
near where you tackled me,
키스하려고했던데
tried to kiss me.
총은 찾았나?
Did you guys find the gun?
- 총을 찾아보기는 했어?
- 애가 도망치는거 봤으면
- Did you even look for a gun?
- Well, if you saw the kid take off,
왜 쫓아가지 그랬어요?
why didn't you chase after him?
있지 난 마약중독자인척 하고있었어
Lady, I was playing a drug addict.
내 잠복근무를 날려먹지 않는이상
걔를 쫓아갈순없잖아
Couldn't go down and chase
him without blowing my cover.
지금처럼 중요하짆 않았어
Not like it matters now.
가도 될까?
Do you mind?
우리 그 집으로 다시 가야되요
Hey, we need to go back to the house.
우린 아무것도 안해도되 알겠지?
We don't need to do anything, okay?
- 더이상 이야기 하고싶지도 않아
- 하지만 제가 정보좀 가져왔어요
- I don't even want to have the talk anymore.
- Yeah, but I just got some more information,
살인사건이랑 연결해
봐야되요
And we need need to to
relay it to homicide.
잠복근무하던 남자랑 얘기했어요
I talked to the undercover guy.
알았어
Fine.
너가 운전해
You drive.
난 소화해야되서
I'll digest.
네
Okay.
야...
Dude...
probation이야 o랑 같이
It's "probation" with an "o"...
pra bation이 아니라
Not "pra-bation."
How was I supposed to know you're
allowed to make a deal with a junkie?
내가 어떻게 알겠어 우리가
마약중독자랑 거래를 해도되는지
가위바위보로..
살인사건이 제일 우선이니깐
이제는 알잖아
Uh, rock, paper, scissors...
homicide trumps all.
- 내가 맹세하는데
- Now we know.
- I swear to God.
이거 입고선 오줌싸는데
15분은 걸린다
It takes 15 minutes to
pee with this thing on.
조는 어딨어?
W... where's Joe?
감사해요 정말 감사해요
Oh, thank you. Thank you so much.
그 유모는 짤라야겠네요
Well, you need to fire that babysitter.
네,네 벌써 했죠
Yeah, yeah, I already did.
그녀한테 메세지만 10개는 남겼어요
I left her, like, ten messages.
유모가 여자인가요?
Yeah, yeah, babysitter's a "her"?
뭐라고요?
Excuse me?
아뇨 그냥 조가
계속 말하길
Well, it's just that's
what Joe kept saying...
"이제 어떻게 그가 날 찾겠어요"
"now how's he gonna find me?"
조가말하길 당신둘이 게임을한다고해서요
He says it's a game you guys play.
조가 그랬어요?
He said that?
제말은 그게 정말 더러운 게임이거든요
I mean, 'cause that's a hell of a game...
8살짜리 아이를
옷장에 남겨두는건
leaving your 8-year-old
kid in a closet...
다 쓰러져가는 집에
in a crack house....
살인사건 이후에
after a homicide.
제가 말했잖아요..
유모랑 있었다니깐요
Look, I told you...
he was with his sitter.
네 전 그냥 당신이
가기전에 그녀한테 전화해볼께요
Yeah, I'm just gonna give
her a call before you leave.
당신이 말하는게 맞는지 확인만하게요
Just make sure your stories line up.
조, 너 잠깐
Joe, you want to, uh,
잠깐 앉아있을래?
just take a seat for a second?
How long have you been using?
사용한지 얼마나 됬죠?
뭐라고요?
What?
- 순경이 질문을 했습니다
- 저도 질문은 들었습니다
- Sir, the officer asked you a question.
- I heard the question.
사실 무슨말을 하는지
모르겠군요 알겠죠?
Honestly, I don't know what
you're talking about, okay?
정말인가요?
Really?
없는 번호랍니다
Hmm. Number's out of service.
알겠어요
All right.
제가 그 상황이면
If I put myself there,
당신이 어딨는지 알겠어요
and right where you are,
제가 이해해요
I get it. You know I do.
하지만 제가 이해못하겟는건
당신이 조를 어떻게 방치했는지에요
But what I do not get is how you left him.
당신은 그냥 거기에 조를 놔뒀어요
I mean, you just left him there alone.
아니에요
I didn't.
조를 혼자 두지 않았어요
I... I didn't leave him alone.
나는..
I, uh...
3번이나 조한테 돌아왔었어요
I went back three times.
그곳이 차단되서..
The place was closed off.
I, uh...
들어갈수가 없었어요
I couldn't get in.
네
Yeah.
가서 아들이랑 이야기하세요
Sir, you should go talk to your son.
아빠가 정말 미안하다
I'm so sorry.
스와락에 의하면,
마이크 월척이 아니라고 왜지?
According to Swarek, it's
not Mike Kowalchuk, why?
그가 말하길" 그는 족제비지만
Uh, he said, "because he's a weasel,
총은없고 남자도 아니다"라고
but he doesn't have the balls or a gun."
- 스와락이 위에있었고?
- 네, 3층에 있었죠
- And Swarek was up there?
- Yeah, he was on the third floor
그리고 오렌지 셔츠입은
남자를 봤다고합니다
and said he saw a guy in an orange shirt
소방계단을 내려가서
저기있는 빌딩으로 가는걸
run down the fire escape and
go into the building over there.
- 제가 가서 확인해 보겠습니다
- 혹시 뭐라도 발견하면 만지지는마
- You know, I can go take a look right now.
- I... if you find anything, don't touch it, huh?
- 그냥 날 부르면 내가 감식반 보낼께
- 네
- Just call me. I'll send in forensics.
- Okay.
- 같이 가주지
- 네
- I'll walk you.
- All right.
그를 체포했다고 들었는데
I hear you arrested him.
- 샘 스와락이요? 네 그랬죠 바보가된것같아요
- 네 잘못이 아니야
- Sam Swarek? Yeah, I did. I feel like an idiot.
- It's not your fault.
다른쪽으로 보면,
꽤 인상적이야
Another context, it's
actually pretty impressive.
- 루크 캘러한
- 앤디 맥넬리
- Luke Callaghan.
- Andy McNally.
- 저희 아버지도 살해쪽에서 일해요
- 오
- Um, yeah, my dad worked homicide, too.
- Oh.
본사에서 일하시나요?
So you work out of headquarters?
아니 난 조 말티닐리 대책위원회의
선두 수사관이야
No, I'm the lead investigator
on the Zoe Martinelli task force,
- 2년동안 하고있지
- 좋네요
- have been for two years.
- Cool.
그녀가 살해당한 15사단의
신입이었서 난 15사단에서 일해
She was a rookie cop killed
in 15, so I work out of 15.
그럼 다시 볼겠네요
Oh. So I guess I'll see you.
물론 제가 무언가
찾으면 당연히 보겠죠
I mean, I'll... I'll definitely
see you if I find anything.
사실 아마도 바로 돌아올거에요
Um, actually, I'll probably be right back.
- 여기있겠네
- 네
- I'll be here.
- Okay.
Ooh.
"그럼 다시 볼겠네요"
"So I guess I'll see you."
Okay.
Oh, God!
Oh!
아 젠장
Oh, crap.
Oh!
움직이지마!
Don't move!
알았어..안녕
Oka... hi.
움직이지 말라니깐!
I said don't move!
- 좋아 손은 위로해
- 알았어x2
- All right, put your hands in the air.
- All right. All right.
- 땅에 엎드려!
- 와우 너정말 좋은 경찰로 만드는구나
- And get down on the ground!
- Wow, you'd make a really good cop.
- 손을 뻗어서 수갑꺼내
- 알았어
- Reach down and take out the cuffs.
- Okay.
빨리! 꺼내란말야!x2
Come on! Take them out! Take them out!
- 수갑채워 빨리!
- 알았어
- Put them on! Cuff yourself! Come on! Okay!
- All right.
그냥 이름이 뭔지
말하지 않을래 응?
Don't you just tell me
what your name is, okay?
- 그 총으로 뭐하고 있는거야?
- 그냥 여기서 주웠어 알겠어 ?
- What you doing with that gun?
- I... I found it. It... it was here, okay?
- 그래 내가 그거 찾으러 여기온거야
- 맥넬리 지금 어딨어?
- Yeah, I know. I came in here to look for it.
- McNally, what's your 20?
- 움직이지 말라니깐!
- 알았어 미안 습관이라서 그래!
- I said don't move!
- Okay! Sorry, it's a habit, all right?
아직 습관은 아니야
내가 새로들어와서
Well, it's not really a
habit yet 'cause I'm new,
하지만 습관으로 만들려고 노력하고있어
but I'm trying to make it a habit,
이게 중요해서....
'cause it's... it's important, so...
내가 여기 사진좀 찍을테니깐
I'm gonna get a few shots in here.
위로 올라가서
사진좀 찍는게 어떤가
Why don't you go upstairs
and get some shots
- 창문이랑 바닥들
- 헤이,루크?
- out that second-floor
window? - Hey, Luke?
- 응?
- 내 신입봤나? 무전 응답을 안해서
- Yeah?
- Have you seen my rookie? She's not answering her radio.
- 쉽게쉽게해 첫날이잖아
- 그래,맥넬리 지금 어디야?
- Go easy on her. It's her first day.
- Yeah. McNally, what's your 20?
- 밖에서 증거찾고 있을거야
- 정말로 그게 진짜인줄 알았어?
- She's outside, looking for evidence.
- Aw, come on, pal. You think that's for real?
스와락 진짜 화났다니깐
Swarek's really pissed off.
- 그거 복수로 헛수고 시키는거야
내가 한번 본적있지
- 어쨋든 거기가 그녀가 있는데야
- That's a payback goose
chase if I've ever seen one.
- Well, that's where she is.
넌 내가 어딨는지 아니깐
Well, you know where I am.
있지..
Listen, um...
말해줘.. 네가 왜
tell me why you, uh...
다른방에서 왜
그남자를 쐇는지...
you shot the guy in the...
in the other room, huh?
당신도..당신도 거기있었어?
What, you were... you were in there?
- 그래
- 당신이랑 누구 ?
- Yeah.
- You and who else?
거기엔
내 트레이닝 경관이랑
Uh, there was, um,
my... my training officer
매춘부랑...
and a... a prostitute, um...
바닥에 여자에도 있었지
마약 과다복용이었어
There was a girl on the
floor. She was overdosing.
몇몇 다른 사람들...
Uh... a couple... other people.
그녀한테 무슨일있었어
What happened to her?
그녀한테 무슨일있었...
What happened to the...
바닥에 있는 여자애는?
girl on the floor?
그녀는 괜찮아x2
She's okay. She's okay.
숨시고있어
그녀는 죽지 않았어
She's, um, she's
breathing. She didn't die.
지금 병원에 있어
She's at the hospital right now.
Hey, I wouldn't even
think about running, okay?
나라면 도망칠려고
생각하지도 않겠어 알겠지?
밖에 경찰들 많아 알겠지?
There's a lot of cops out there. Okay?
So why don't you just tell
me what happened, okay?
그냥 나한테
무슨일있었는지 말하는게어때 응?
넌 ...
You can't be...
18살도 아닐테니깐 다 괜찮을거야
can't be 18, so everything is go.
괜찮을꺼야
내가 도울수있어 알겠지?
You're gonna be okay. I
can help you. All right?
- 내가 바닥에있으랬잖아!!
- 알았어x2
- Hey, I told you to stay down, all right?!
- All right. All right.
움직이지마! 제발 움직이지마
Don't move! All right, please don't move.
갑작스런 행동하면
내가 방아쇠를 당겨야되
Any sudden movements, and
I gotta pull the trigger.
그게 절차야
That's procedure.
사실 벌써
했어야되지만
Actually, technically, I
should have done it already.
제발 그냥 총 내려와
알겠지 느리게
Come on. Just please put
the gun down, okay? Slowly.
총내려놔 제발좀!
Put the gun down. Come on, man!
제발 내가 널쏘게 만들지마
Okay, please don't make me shoot you.
내 첫날이라고
너한테 빈다 부탁이야
This is my first day.
I'm begging you, please!
제발x2
Come on. Come on.
부탁이야
I'm begging you.
제발 내가 도와줄수있어
Come on. I can help you, okay?
그냥 내려놔
Just put it down.
Come on.
- 그녀는 15살이에요
- 누구?
- She's 15.
- Who?
내 여동생이요
My sister.
안에있던 여자애..
The... the girl inside.
- 그리고 걔는 그냥 바닥에 누워있었어요
- 그래?
- And she was just laying there...
- Yeah?
- 그리고 움직이질 않았어요
- 그래,그래
- And she wasn't moving.
- Okay, okay.
- 모든게 너무 빨리 지나갔어요 그남자..
- 누구 ?
- It all happened so fast. That guy... the...
- What guy?
- 그..
- 누구..?
- The g...
- What guy?
마약상?
Drug dealer?
걔가 죽은줄 알았어요
I thought she was dead.
그한테 계속물었죠
I kept asking him,
무슨일이냐고
그녀가 뭘복용했는지 말해달라고
"wh... what happened?
Tell me what she took."
그러더니 그는 그게 웃기듯이 비웃었어요
Then he just laughed like it funny.
그가 말하길...
He said...
그가 말하길 그건 걔 잘못이래요
그는 그녀를 그냥 거기에 놔두고있었어요
he said it was her fault,
said he was leaving her there.
마치 쓰레기인마냥
바닥에 놔두고있었어요
Leaving her there on the
floor like a piece of garbage!
너는, 너는
I know. It was her fault, and you...
and you... stop him from leaving.
넌 그가 그냥 놔두는걸 멈춘거고 그렇지?
You stopped him from leaving, right?
그리고 넌 여기들어와서
총을 숨겼고
And then you came in
here and you hid the gun.
그리고 지금은
총때문에 온거고 그렇지?
And now you just came
back for the gun, right?
그럴 생각은 없었어요
I still didn't mean to do it.
나도 알아 미안하다
I know. Come on. I'm sorry, man.
괜찮아 미안해
난 이걸 해야만해 알겠지?
It's okay. I'm sorry. I gotta
do this, though, all right?
괜찮아
It's okay.
Okay.
가자 괜찮지?
Let's go, okay?
내가 병원에 전화해봤어 그리고
I called the hospital and, uh...
- 그애 여동생...괜찮데
- 굿
- That guy's little sister... she made it.
- Good.
그거 잘됐네요
걔한테 말해줘야되요
Good, that's great. Yeah,
you should probably tell him.
그래 아니 좋은거는
그녀 피가 깨끗하다는거야
Yeah. No, what's great is
that her blood work is clear.
- 하지만 아직 너 테스트는 받아야되
- 네
- All right, you still have to get tested, okay?
- Yeah.
- 음,내가 한때 맥넬리라는 남자랑 일했었는데
- Well, I, uh, I used to work with a guy named McNally.
- Oh.
옛날일이지, 그가 오랫동안
내 트레이닝 경관이었는
Uh, long time ago. He was my
training officer for awhile,
하지만 그는..좀..
but he... kind of... I...
Well, I heard that he hit
a rough patch awhile back,
하지만 음..그는 언제나 좋은사람이었어
but, uh... but he was always a good guy.
네 그렇죠..
Yeah, he is.
뭐 어쨋든
그냥 말해주고싶었어
Yeah, anyway, I just
wanted to say that, uh...
"새로운 페인트" 경계 있잖아
"Fresh paint" line from before?
그건 그사람꺼였어
That was his.
그가 책에서 얻었는디
어디서 얻었는지는 몰라..
I don't know if he got
it from a book or...
어느쪽이던 그가 처음이었으니깐
You know, either way, it was his first.
난 그냥
I just, uh...
나도 모르겠어..난
그냥 언제나 그걸 좋아했어 알지?
I don't know. I just... I
always liked it, you know?
네 x2
Yeah. Yeah.
헤이 루크
Hey, Luke?
Yeah.
감사해요
Thanks.
Hi.
- 힘든 하루였지
- 네
- Quite a day.
- Yeah.
이게 두번째...
This is the second of...
- 20번째
- 4번 5번? 20번째
- 20.
- 4 or 5. 20? Okay.
- 그리고 하나더 부탁해요
- 드릴게요
- And one more, please?
- Coming up.
순경
Officer.
형사님
Detective.
언제 가는지 알려주면
집까지 태워다 드리죠
Let me know when you're
leaving. I'll drive you home.
고맙지만
오늘밤 계획이 있어서요
Uh, thank you, but,
uh, I got plans tonight.
Hey.
오늘 팁 고마웠어요
Thanks for the tip today.
잘해냈던데
Worked out pretty good.
그럼 제가 술이라도 한잔...
Yeah. So can I buy you a drink...
고맙다고 아니면 사과의미로
say thank you or apologize?
안톤 힐 누군지 아나?
Anton Hill... you know who he is?
아뇨
No.
70퍼센트의 헤로인이
안톤을 통해서 도시로 오지
70% of the heroin that comes
into city comes through Anton,
안톤이 여자애랑
놀고있을때
when he's not pimping
little girls for fun.
8개월동안 잠복근무중이었지
I was undercover eight months.
그 남자를 체포하기까지
딱 2주남았었지
I was two weeks away
from arresting the guy.
너만의 개성을 가져서 기쁘네,
I'm glad you got your collar,
하지만 오늘밤
내술은 내가사겠어
but I think I'll buy
my own drinks tonight.
알겠어요
Okay.
새로운날,새로운 나쁜놈
Hey, another day, another dirtbag.
- 보이고씨가 말했던건가?
- 봉사하고 보호하고 ..
- What is it Boyko was saying?
- Um... serve, protect, and...
그리고 망치지 말라고
And don't screw up.
내가 어떻게 그가
잠복근무중이라는걸 알았겠어 응?
How was I supposed to
know he's undercover, huh?
내말은 이게 칭찬해줘야
되잖아 그렇지?
I mean, it's a compliment,
really. Isn't it?
누가 신경써, 너가 그놈 잡았잖아
Who cares? You caught that kid.
너가 너 스스로 그놈 데려왔잖아
You brought him out all by yourself.
수갑이랑 살인도구도 ?
Handcuffs, murder weapon?
대단한데 맥넬리
Rock 'n' roll, McNally.
- 그래 그거지
- "트레이시 첫날이잖아
- Yeah, right?
- "Yeah, Traci, it's our first day.
우린 아무것도 안해도되
그냥 앉아있으면
We don't have to do
anything but sit there,
- 그들이 운전해줄꺼야"
- 시끄러
- and they'll just drive us around."
- Oh, shut up.
26...
25...
6...
Six...
5...
Five...
4...
Four...
3...
Three...
2...
Two...
- 1
- 0분
- One!
- Zero minutes.
- 안녕 내 (아들?)
- 안녕
- Hello, my...
- Hi!
- Mmm
- Mmm.
아빠
Dad, hey. Hey.
그래서? 어땠어?
So? How was it?
좋았어요..
It was good.
엉망이었어요
It was terrible.
잘모르겠어요
I don't know. I don't know.
그건 괜찮은거니..?
You gonna be... you gonna be okay?
네
Oh, yeah.
괜찮을거에요
I'll be fine.
첫날이 언제나 최고란다
Ah, first days are always the best.
새로운 부츠에 새로운 배지에
New boots, new badge.
온 세상 냄새가 새로운 페인트 냄새같지
Whole world smells like fresh paint.
계속 그대로
지구를 유지하고싶지
You've been set on earth
to keep it that way.
신입냄새가 새 페인트
냄새 같은줄 알았는데요
Thought it was the rookies
that smelled like fresh paint.
넌 괜찮을거다
Ah, you're gonna be fine.
넌 진짜니깐
'Cause you're the real deal,
진짜 재앙인
이 늙은이와는 다르게
unlike your old man,
who's a total catastrophe.
내가 널위해 가지고있던게 있다
I've been, uh...
아빠
Dad.
가족을 가까이해라
Keep it in the family.
기억하렴
You remember...
넌 앤디 맥넬리고
잘해낼꺼라고
you're Andy McNally, and
you're gonna be great.
피드백
http://benbearlee.tistory.com/
sync by yyets.net - corrected by chamallow
www.addic7ed.com